Android 1.0在2008年发布了  在仅仅六年之后
Android 1.0 launched in 2008. And in just the six year since then,
有11个新的平台发布  在Android开发方面
there has been 11 new major platform releases. On the Android developer side,
我们在一个给定的图标中展示了数量相对活跃的Android设备运行的平台版本
we show the relative number of active Android devices running a given platform
饼图真的是非常棒的  但是对于我们的目的来说
version in this pie chart, because pie charts are awesome. For our purposes
你真的最好还是考虑看一下这个直方图  如果你眯着眼睛
though, you're really better off looking at this as a histogram. If you squint,
你大约可以看到一个模糊的钟形曲线  最早的Android版本是在这里
you can almost see a vaguely bell-shaped curve, with the oldest releases here at
它们的知名度随着设备的升级和更换而逐渐下降
the left, their popularity dropping off as devices are upgraded or
在中间的是在设备中所占比例最大的
replaced. The largest proportion of devices are here in the middle,
代表着这些设备已经两岁啦  而最新的平台
representing devices about two years old. And the newest platforms,
日益普及的新手机在发布和升级
gaining popularity as new phones are released or upgrades go out,
在它的右侧  所以考虑到这一点  最低SDK作为您的最低限度
are here on the right. So with that in mind, the Min SDK acts as your low-pass
Google Play将不会在一台比最低SDK版本还低的设备平台上显示您的应用程序
filter. Google Play won't show your app on devices running a platform version
所以我们为什么不只设置一项最低SDK而支持所有的设备呢
lower than its minimum SDK version. So why not just set the Min SDK to one and
一般来说  你想要让你的目标SDK满足尽可能多的用户
support everyone? Generally, you'll want to target as many users as you can, but
但要与一些旧的版本进行匹配是要付出代价的
there's a cost associated with supporting some of these older versions.
比如像创建不同的执行路径都不可用
Things like creating different execution paths around deprecated or
或更新API呈现一种带有不同功能的不一样的用户体验
update APIs or presenting a different UX to devices with different features. So
所以你需要平衡扩展你的应用的受众所付出的代价是否值得
you need to balance the opportunity of expanding your audience with the cost of
同时  记住每个版本都介绍了它的新的API和硬件支持
supporting those new users. Also, remember that each release introduced with it
因此  把您的应用程序在不支持
new APIs and hardware support. So it may not make sense to
你的最小功能集的设备上运行是没有意义的
make your app available to devices that don't support your minimum feature set.
通过比较  目标SDK不是一个最高限度
By comparison, the Target SDK is not a high-pass filter.
它只是用来声明你所测试过的平台的版本
It's used only to declare which platform version you've tested on.
针对一个特定的API的应用将继续在后续的版本中向前兼容
An app targeted to a certain API will continue to be forward compatible on
该平台使用目标SDK的值以防
future releases. The platform uses the Target SDK values in case a future
后续的平台显著的改变预期的行为
platform makes a significant change to expected behavior. This ensures your app
这样可以确保您的应用程序在用户的手机升级的时候仍然可用
doesn't break when a user's phone gets upgraded. If you're developing a new app,
如果你正在开发一个新的应用程序  没有任何理由去针对某一个版本作为目标SDK比使用最新版本的Android更为合适
there's really no reason to target anything but the latest Android version. And
一旦你的应用程序发布  作为重要的一点是更新你的目标SDK
once your app has been released, make it a point to update your Target SDK and
当新的平台发布的时候越快测试越好
test as soon as possible when new platform releases roll out so you can take
这样  你就可以利用每一个新平台的特点来优化和改进您的应用
advantage of every new platform optimization and improvement it has to offer.